http://www.dpdsoftware.ca/privacy-and-confidentiality

Friday, December 11, 2020
DPD SOFTWARE LTD. remains committed to the protection of your information. This statement on the confidentiality and privacy of your information is in compliance with government legislation, Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents (PIPED) Act, and in accordance with established Company policies and procedures.YOUR INFORMATIONIn order to provide you with a minimum level of service, we collect information such as names, job titles, company name, and company contact information including mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers, that is kept on our database as a resource by which to contact you. We may from time to time send you information we believe is relevant to the business we conduct. We do not release any of your contact information to any third party without your authorization.Because of the nature of our business, it is normal for us to be entrusted with priviledged and highly confidential proprietary information from our customers. Any and all information received by DPD Software Ltd. is considered confidential Company information.DPD Software Ltd. maintains an information management system that assigns user accounts, access rights and security authorizations. Each person on our team is bounded by a Confidentiality Agreement. DPD Software's published Security Policy, Confidentiality Policy, and Business Ethics Policy dictates and defines the use and levels of access to any Company information.Through the act of seeking information or services from our company you or your representative may provide us with various contact details that we request. By providing us with this information or by having a representative provide us with this information you are granting us permission to send to you the pieces of information that you have requested including all subsequent transmission of material that we may deem appropriate to send to you.YOUR PRIVACYFurther information on the details of Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents (PIPED) Act can be obtained directly from www.privcom.gc.caYou always have access to your personal information and the right to modify that information. Your comments and questions are always welcomed:If you wish to;* Obtain details on the personal information of you that we have on record
* Correct personal information that we have of you on record
* Make an inquiry or complainte-Mail us at:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it." style="color: rgb(72, 94, 144); font-family: verdana, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 10px;">This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.Or phone us and ask to speak to the Office Administrator (our privacy officer):
204-489-4398
866-489-4398
HomeProducts and Servicese-Business SolutionsCustom Software SolutionsPoint of SaleOffice AutomationWireless ProductsPurple Soft Mobile ERPDownloadsOffice automationMobile ERP BasicsERP Modules and FeaturesStandard ERPPurpleSoft Mobile ERPPartner with usAbout usForewordWhy Choose DPDPhilosophyAffiliationsTestimonialsContact UsOur Point of View
